(Howard:)-I totally had a shot.
-With a woman you were chasing in a park.
(Raj:)That's not a shot, that's a felony.
(Raj:)What's worse, it cost me
my prized Patang fighting kite.
(Raj:)I don't suppose there's any chance
you could give me my kite back?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, Raj,
but the rules of aerial warfare dictate...
...that the fallen kite go to the victor.
(Sheldon:)And without rules,
the competition has no meaning.
(Sheldon:)And without meaning, the following
would be an empty gesture:
[SINGSONGY]
I have your kite, I have your kite
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Penny:)-Hey.
-Hi.
(Leonard:)How was your football party?
(Penny:)-It was pretty good, we won.
-Oh, wow, that's excellent.
Weird figure of speech, isn't it?
"We won,"
when you weren't actually playing.
When we watch Star Wars, we don't say,
"We defeated the Empire." Ha, ha.
(Penny:)I'm glad to hear it.
(Leonard:)Oh, hey, on a related subject...